Guide to the Dennistoun Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - "W"
    - Wemyss, Francis Wemyss Charteris Douglas, 7th Earl of, 1795-1883. ALS to James Dennistoun, Edinburgh, 1854 Nov (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Whyte-Melville, E. C. ALS to Isabella Dennistoun, Mount Melville, 1852 Mar 10 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Whyte-Melville, J. ALS to James Dennistoun, Mount Melville, 1852 Mar 10 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Wilkie Club. Letter (signed by Thomas Duncan) to James Dennistoun, Edinburgh, 1842 Mar (Box 4, Folder 187)
      Notice of General Meeting.
    - Wilson, Charles Heath, 1809-1882. 2 ALS to James Dennistoun, Glasgow, 1850, 1853 (Box 4, Folder 188)
      The teaching of fine arts.
    - Unidentified letters and letter fragments, 1841-53, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 189)
- Other Papers, 1815-33, n.d.; Series II
  - Poems by James Dennistoun: holographs, 1815-33, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 190)
    Includes 1815 translation of the fortieth Ode of Anacreon by James Dennistoun
  - Poem by James Murray of Elibank: holograph, 1832 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    On a collision in the Charlotte Straits
  - Invitations and programs, 1823-42, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Bibliographical information, 1973, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 193)